I get to take home the souvenir video of this when we're done, right?
Jonathan, you can go ahead and put your shirt on.
How does everything look, Dr. Scanlon?
Well, I'm afraid the left ventricular myocardium is still dyskinetic.
Well, I don't like the way that sounds.
Because of your arterial blockage, I'm going to recommend a triple bypass.
You're only in the hospital for a few days.
And I promise you, when you come out, you'll feel better than when you came in.
What? Open heart surgery? Don't you think that's a bit extreme?
We've been friends for a long time.
And I know you can be a stubborn man.
Look, given your current condition, Jonathan, you could have another heart attack any moment.
And the next time could be fatal.
And the surgery could be fatal, too.
Trust me.
You stand a far greater risk if you don't have this operation.
Come on!
Garrett?
Garrett!
Thanks, Clark.
You figure after a couple months, you'll like me better.
Yeah.
I thought your dad was out of the woods.
So did I.
But I...
Here we are again.
How's your brother doing, Garrett?
In serious need of a new liver.
If he doesn't get one soon, I don't know how much time he's got left.
Of course, if he knew I was out here hovering instead of hitting the books, he'd pitch a fit.
What's it looking like for your dad?
You're talking about open heart surgery.
Remember the thing you told me about your father?
I told you, your father should be walking the park.
You know, Garrett, I always thought of my dad as a man of steel.
I guess I was wrong.
Clark, your dad is gonna have that surgery.
And my brother's gonna get that transplant.
And a year from now, we'll all get together and laugh about how freaked out we both were.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I don't really want to do anything.
Look, Grandpa, I've tried to end the career that I've been living.
I've Não for the rest of my life and Vid said it on and on,, he said you need to
settle down and rest properly on , but now you have your own stomach for him.
He may come and get you, but you can't go from there.
Uncle Victor tren s virtual dilemm.
How fast are we on the road to my own home and our family's home?
Put him ferank heaven sire, you got it?
Okay, Billy?
When is it going to be perfect?"
arma ca n en ca caves.
Entre mercury quC n stimulus.
Spence, please!
Spence!
Not yet!
Come on.
Please.
No, stop.
All right.
Let's call it.
Time of death, 2.43 PM.
I'm sorry, son.
...
I made this whole world shine for you
Yeah, yeah, come on
Poor boy.
Where's his family?
His brother's all he had.
His parents died in a car accident when he was a little kid.
Well, who's gonna take care of him?
He's got an uncle in Germany.
It'll take him a few days to get here.
He said something about foster care.
No.
He shouldn't be there the night his brother died.
He can stay with us for a few days.
Are you sure?
What about Dad's surgery and everything?
I overheard.
Dad's not sure he's gonna...
He's not gonna have it yet.
I'm gonna go speak with Dr. Scanlon.
Hi, Clark.
Look, I'm, uh...
Sorry to hear about your friend Garrett.
How's he holding up?
He's in shock.
Guess that's what happens
when the most important person in your life is gone.
I know about the surgery.
Can you believe it?
I'm so popular around here,
they want me to be admitted right away.
So you're gonna do it?
It's not quite that cut and dried, Clark.
There must be a way around this.
No, I heard the doctor.
It didn't sound like that.
I thought you and I talked about it.
I thought you were dropping in
on people's private conversations.
If you'd stop trying to protect me from this,
I wouldn't have to.
Dad, I see Garrett out there, and he's lost.
Just like I'd be without you.
Please do this.
Clark.
I want you to go out there
and tell your mother to start filling out all the admissions paperwork.
Go on.
And, Clark,
don't worry about me, son.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to go.
Mrs. Kent, I want you to know how much I appreciate this.
Oh, sweetheart, we're happy to have you.
Clark, I'm going to go get some things together for your dad.
Garrett, if you want to be alone...
No, I really don't.
It's kind of ironic.
My brother worked in demolition.
I risked his life every day with explosives,
and I lose him to liver disease.
He had just gotten that transplant.
He'd still be.
Your dad's about to have surgery.
You don't need to hear this.
No, Garrett, it helps to talk about it.
You listened to me that time in the hospital.
Part of me feels like Vince isn't really gone.
That it's all just some...
some big misunderstanding.
Garrett, if there's anyone that needs to be told,
I can help.
Make some phone calls.
No, it was just us.
He used to call me Ron as long as I can remember.
I always hated it,
and I'd give anything to hear him say it again.
Garrett,
I just got a call from the crematorium.
They want to know where they should send your brother's ashes.
Ashes?
What are they talking about?
He's supposed to be buried next to my mom and dad.
Let's move.
Okay, well,ja...
They're here.
Sringe.
Welcome back, Vince.
Dr., why would you have him cremated.
That couldn't be the same Vincent Davis.
That's what the paperwork says.
All the documents are signed,
including your brother's autograph on that cremation form.
No.
Look, maybe you didn't know him as well as you thought you did.
What are you talking about?
Garrett, calm down.
How am I supposed to be calm
when my brother's been carved up and burned to a crisp?
Look, son, I know this is difficult, but...
You don't know anything.
I'm sorry.
Garrett, I know this is hard.
Maybe Vince just didn't tell you.
My brother's told me everything since the day my parents died.
Those documents have to be forged.
Well, I think your embassy would keep tabs on North Koreans
who have recently been deported.
Seems like Dr. Tang has vanished
from the public eye.
Without a trace.
Yeah, well, it turns out that's not the only thing
out of the ordinary of our friendly molecular biologist.
What have you got?
Well, it turns out it wasn't scientific research
or academic prestige that got her into this country 12 years ago.
It was wedding bells.
She married a rent-a-cop from Luther Corp.
So my father arranged a green card marriage.
Yeah.
Now, I tracked down the groom so I could ask him what he knew.
What'd the lucky guy have to say?
Wasn't really what he had to say.
It was more where he said it.
He plays watchdog for the old Metron Pharmaceuticals building.
That's been shut down for seven years.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
But while he was in the process of telling me to get lost,
I swear I saw what I think was a delivery
truck pulling around back.
My father's been strangely stubborn about liquidating
that property.
Every market indicates his worth, but nothing else.
Oh, no.
says to sell, but he insists the neighborhood's
about to be revitalized.
The only thing being revitalized in that neighborhood
is the graffiti.
Now, I think I can make some headway if you'll
just come along with me.
Chloe, I think I should take it from here.
Lex, I'm perfectly capable of doing it.
This has nothing to do with your capability.
I'm worried about your safety.
When my father's involved with covert research,
people tend to get hurt.
I'm sorry I lost it.
I guess I kind of have a sharp fuse.
You have every reason to be upset, Garrett.
Thing is, it just doesn't make any sense.
Vince?
It's me, Rhett.
I can't believe it.
This is incredible.
Wait, I don't understand.
We both saw you.
You were pronounced dead.
I guess they were wrong.
Well, there's got to be an explanation.
All I know is when I woke up, I was in a lab,
and this woman doctor with a needle the size of Kansas
was standing over me.
Come on, Rhett.
We have to get out of here.
Wait, we should get you to a doctor.
No more doctors or labs.
Garrett and I have to fall off the radar.
Why?
Who's after you?
I don't know, but.
You tell me where the lab is?
Uh, it's, uh, somewhere in Metropolis.
Are you OK?
Garrett, let's roll.
Vince?
Your eyes, they're bleeding.
What's happening to him?
Vince?
Vince, no.
Clark, you have to help him, please.
No, I don't know how to explain it.
This man was dead yesterday.
He said he was revived at a lab in Metropolis.
Whatever they did, it was short term.
I'm afraid he's not going to be able to last much longer.
His liver is rapidly deteriorating.
Dr. Yeager, just call the lab and tell him to give him more of whatever he got.
I have no idea what lab you're talking about.
Don't hold out on me.
I'm not going to stand here until my brother dies again.
Look, I've never had a patient come back to life before.
I'm just as confounded as you are.
But I promise you, we're doing everything we can to keep your brother alive.
All right, here we go.
I'm not sure coming back here was such a great idea.
There's no other place to take him, Garrett.
At least here, they can try to stabilize him.
I can't lose him twice, Clark.
How's Dad doing?
I feel like I'm being prepped for a Thanksgiving dinner,
and I'm the turkey.
Not a good scar to brag about.
Clark, what's happening with Garrett's brother?
He's going downhill fast, and the doctors,
they don't know what to do.
But he mentioned this lab in Metropolis.
If I could find it, maybe I could figure out what cured him.
You need to go help your friend, Clark.
No, Dad, I'm not leaving you.
Clark, I'm in very capable hands here,
and honestly, you're not very good sitting on the sidelines.
Garrett and Vince need you, Clark.
Yeah, but, son, if there's any chance
that you could save your friend's life,
then that's what you need to do.
Dad, I want you to know...
I do know, Clark.
And I love you.
I love you, too.
Now go on.
Help your friend.
Clark.
I thought you and your mom could use some moral support
and a little sustenance.
Thanks, Lana.
My mom hasn't eaten all day.
I'm sure she'll appreciate it.
I'll be back soon.
Is everything all right?
Do you know Garrett Davis?
Sure.
He and Vince used to come by the town.
Yeah, well, Vince came down with this rare liver disease,
and he needed a transplant.
I'm guessing from the past tense that he never got it.
No, he died yesterday.
Then last night, he showed up at my barn.
He came back to life?
He seemed completely fine
until he started bleeding from his eyes.
I've seen it before.
With Adam, I...
I found this obituary that said he died five months ago
of a rare liver disease.
Did you tell anyone?
Why not?
Adam said if I told anyone, they could be in danger.
Where is Adam now?
I don't know.
He disappeared.
I haven't seen him in more than a week.
Listen, Vince mentioned he got an injection.
He said he was in a state of emergency.
I don't know if he's still in there.
I don't know.
Did Adam ever take anything?
Yeah.
At first I thought it was because he was a drug addict,
but maybe that's what was keeping him alive.
Yeah, you're right.
Vince.
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
No disease.
None of this is your fault.
But if it weren't for me, you could have had such a better life.
You would have married and had kids of your own instead of worrying about me.
Garrett, I wouldn't have done it any different.
Even if you are a runt, you're not a drug addict.
You're a drug addict.
Garrett?
There's not much else we can do at this point except make him comfortable.
Now might be a good time to say your goodbyes.
I'm not saying goodbye to anybody.
Son, I know this is hard.
I'm not gonna let him die.
Do you hear me? I'm not gonna let him die!
When he's ready, you have to let him go.
When that day comes, you'll be standing right beside me.
We're ready.
You know, Clark, I can totally run with this if you want to go be with your dad.
It's all right. He knows I'm here.
Besides, it takes my mind off the fact I can't do anything for him.
Everything's gonna be okay.
We need to figure out what brought Vince back to life.
Well, it looks like my contact at Metropolis General emailed me.
The only organ donors who arrived yesterday were both females.
That means Medivac Chopper took Garrett's brother somewhere else.
Seems that Flyboy's the one to talk to.
I'm sure he's got a lot of work to do.
Are you Ben Powell?
What's it to you?
Where'd you take that body yesterday?
Look, uh, I don't know what kind of game you think you're playing,
but I'm an emergency medical pilot.
You left here to take a body to Metropolis General, and that body never arrived.
Now, I'm not a lawyer, but I'm willing to guess you could do some pretty serious jail time
for using a Medivac helicopter for your own profit.
What do you want?
Take me where you took Vincent Davis.
What is this place?
They pay me cash, I don't ask questions.
You don't have to ask me.
Holmes, I always have you under control.
Now, enough with the
prix
Who's there?
I thought I'd never see you again.
What are you doing here?
So this is where you were deported to.
I can only imagine the moves you used to sway the immigration officers.
How did you get past security?
As I'm sure you're well aware, this building is owned by Luther Corps.
A family name tends to open doors.
This looks familiar.
It's identical to the vial found in Adam Knight's apartment.
It's a very delicate substance.
If you don't leave at once, I'm notifying your father.
Can't you just send me to the principal instead?
I offered to fund your research, Doctor.
You turn your back on me.
Now, I suggest you tell me the origin of your little blood-platelet cocktail,
or I'll make sure the I.N.S. reserves you a window seat on the next flight to Pyongyang.
Something tells me they don't look too kindly at North Koreans doing illegal research on American soil.
Where did it go?
I don't know.
I just want to be sure.
What did you just do?
Are you ready to proceed?
Yes.
Go ahead, start it.
I want two more milligrams of potassium chloride in the I.V.
Yes, Doctor.
Vitals.
Pulse is leveled off at 80.
BP 120 over 70.
EKG normal.
normal blood ox 98 normal okay jonathan we're gonna have you out of here in no time
i suppose all we can do now is wait mr kent strong he's gonna fight through this
pete i wasn't sure if you guys wanted your space but at the end of the day i thought i should be
here oh i'm so glad you came where's clark he'll be right back okay dr jaeger
where is dr jaeger
i want to speak to dr jaeger just what do you think you're doing my brother needs a liver
so i figure now you'll get him one garrett this isn't gonna solve anything don't come any closer
if you want anyone to leave this building with their limbs attached
you better make sure my brother gets that transplant
oh
come on
sheriff
just hold it hey not now mr kent you know you can't tell i am a little busy here
my parents are in there my dad's having surgery please what's going on let him go
there is a kid in there who's gonna blow this place to kingdom come unless his brother gets a transplant
You know him?
His brother doesn't need a transplant.
I have medicine that can cure him.
Where would you get this wonder drug?
It doesn't matter. Please, if you tell him I have this,
we can prevent anyone from getting hurt.
Sheriff, I know him. He's just desperate.
Well, desperate equals dangerous in my book.
Sheriff, please.
Just get him on the phone. He'll talk to me.
We have a serious problem.
Clark can't help us in here.
That bomb is laced with meteor rock.
His family uses it for their demolition business.
More bang for their buck.
Mrs. Kent, you're a nice lady. I don't want to hurt you.
Don't do this, Garrett.
It's not what your brother would want.
I know exactly what my brother wanted.
A transplant and to see me graduate high school.
I'm gonna make sure he gets both of those,
even if I have to be locked up when I get that diploma.
Yeah?
Garrett, it's Clark.
Listen, I tracked down the lab they took Vince to,
and I grabbed a vial of the medicine that they gave him.
I'm holding it right here in my hand.
Why should I trust you?
Because I've done nothing but try to help you.
Okay. Come in, but just you.
No. I will not allow that.
I will get one of my deputies to bring it in.
It's Clark or no one.
You have to let the hostages go.
It's the only way they're even gonna think about letting me in.
Clark!
Mom, are you okay?
I'm fine.
But your father's still in the operating room.
Clark, Garrett means what he says.
I just need to get this medicine to Vince,
and I'll take care of the bomb.
Clark, you may not be able to.
It's made with kryptonite.
Be careful.
There's too much at stake here.
You can find a good vantage point.
You get a clean shot, you take him out.
Garrett!
Where is it?
It's right here.
What are you doing?
Garrett, you have a bomb strapped to your chest.
I'd prefer to just keep my distance.
The poppy's getting a little crazy.
Completely yakking for that.
Aunt proceso-
Why is this taboo?
I'm telling the truth,
my brother and his mother hadアpathy with me.
Return your medicine tunas,
my business.
Dalek is even looking for the confidence
I need over here.
Or is he?
Is this the hospital?
What is this?
Just do it.
Please, just do it.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry!
How long is this supposed to take, Clark?
I'm not sure.
There's no change in his vitals.
It's not working?
You lied to me, Clark.
No, I didn't.
That's it. My brother's getting a liver now.
We don't have to.
You have one, Garrett.
Yes, you do. You've got a man lying in the O.R.
That's my dad.
I don't have another choice.
No, you're not touching him.
Clark!
You'll still have a mom.
If Vince dies, I have no one.
Son, the chances of success are very low.
Just go.
Now!
Doctor, you can't do this.
I know I can't.
There are 20 other patients in this.
I don't know what to do.
You don't want to do this, Garrett.
I'm sorry, Clark.
I'm sorry.
You're in trouble.
No!
Take me!
I'm sorry.
It's okay, Dad.
It's okay.
Don't worry about him.
He matches me in the caiters and Krydleys,
and only Paul interests me here.
You're so fine with that, Garrett.
Is everyone alright?
Everything's stable?
Let's continue.
Your father wanted to cut off his medication.
He said Adam Knight's role in the project was done,
but I couldn't do it.
It was barbaric. It would have killed him.
That's why you've hidden him down here from my father.
Why don't you just keep the kid on the medicine?
The platelets are an extremely short supply.
You still haven't told me where these blood platelets come from.
I don't know.
Why would I lie to you?
You're my only way out from your father's grip.
But I do know they have the remarkable ability
to revivify necrotic tissue.
So why is it that all the subjects suffer from the same liver disease?
The cells in the liver are the most resilient cells in the body.
I want you to relax, Adam.
It's me, Dr. Tang.
What's wrong with him?
He's deteriorating.
I told your father not to rush the serum's development,
but he wouldn't listen.
I don't think it's going to get much cleaner.
What brings you to the far reaches of the town?
Ellen.
Well, I thought I might be able to find a clue
to the former tenant's whereabouts.
Why?
He's gone.
That's what's important.
You wouldn't happen to know where he is, would you?
No.
I just want to forget that he ever lived here.
Yeah, I can see that.
Lana.
Is there something you're not telling me?
No.
Of course not.
I guess I'm going to have to put all this stuff in storage.
Look.
I want you to know
if you ever feel like talking about Adam,
I'm always here.
Lex.
Why are you still interested in him, anyway?
He came to me and asked if I can get him out of your life.
I'm just following up and making sure he stays that way.
Here.
You don't know by now.
Hey, um, thanks for the lift.
I think I can take it from here.
Easy, Jonathan. The doctor said to stand slowly.
If I stand any slower, I'll be standing still.
Thank you so much for everything. Bye-bye.
Hey, Clark.
It's all right, son. The doctor says that...
The worst of this is behind me.
Hey, Clark?
What's bothering you, son?
When I went to pick up the vial for Vince, Lex was there.
He was talking to one of the scientists.
From their conversation, it sounds like Lionel Luther's behind all of it.
I don't know.
Now, why doesn't that surprise me?
Dad, when that serum got close to the kryptonite bomb,
it reacted the same way as my blood.
So you're saying the serum...
I know. It sounds crazy, but I think that Lionel Luther's
found a way to use my blood to bring people back to life.
If my blood can save lives,
maybe I should come forward.
What if there's something inside me that could repair Dad's heart?
Permanently?
Clark.
Your mother and I both know
that you are going to save a lot of lives in this world.
Even more than you have any idea.
The only life I'm interested in saving is yours.
You do.
You save my life every day that you're with us.
And we wouldn't trade that for a single moment without you.
Hey.
Hey. How's your dad feeling?
Oh, you never know. He just had a triple bypass.
My mom actually bought the doctor a combat helmet as a thank you gift.
Your dad could survive surgery during a siege.
Thank you.
I talked to Garrett's uncle. He wanted to know what happened.
What'd you say?
I couldn't explain Vince's resurrection,
but I told him that Garrett was a good kid.
You know, he was desperate.
He wanted to do whatever he could to save his brother.
You should have said something about Adam sooner.
I feel so guilty.
None of this was your fault.
Still, I let him threaten me to silence.
Because you knew it would put people in danger.
I understand.
Keeping secrets for that reason.
It was really hard keeping it from everyone.
It was kind of a relief to tell you.
Lana, no matter where we stand,
I'm still your friend.
And you can tell me anything.
You know, that goes both ways.
I love you.
I can't do this all alone,
but I can also make you go,
and I'll make you run away.
Wait, Lena...
You can't cut this.
You know I'll always keep you as my son,
just like you did with popeye.
いや, estoy members.
We'll just have to get through it together out there.
You have to sing for my sake.
Clark.
What do you think was in that serum?
What, through the avianONG?
Dear me.
Dubious himself.
Mad Kate.
I have questions?
Boys who don't trust her.
This is important stuff.
You just need it. nichts deeper.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.